export const elmPrepPlace =[{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "There is a coffee table _________ the couch.",
        "options": [
            "next to",
            "under",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "next to"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Our Latin teacher always stands _________ the teacher's desk.",
        "options": [
            "under",
            "in",
            "in front of",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "in front of"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Mr. Hemmingway has a beautiful garden _________ his house.",
        "options": [
            "under",
            "in",
            "on",
            "behind"
        ],
        "answer": "behind"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Mr. Pinsley, our elf, is _________ the kitchen table.",
        "options": [
            "under",
            "at",
            "behind",
            "in front of"
        ],
        "answer": "under"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Jenni like to play cricket _________ the baseball field.",
        "options": [
            "in front of",
            "in",
            "on",
            "under"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Sabrina is looking for her doll _________ the attic.",
        "options": [
            "in",
            "on",
            "under",
            "in front of"
        ],
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Reggie likes to play with his brother _________ the basketball court.",
        "options": [
            "in",
            "under",
            "behind",
            "next to"
        ],
        "answer": "behind"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "The red dragon sat _________ his treasure.",
        "options": [
            "on",
            "in",
            "under",
            "in front of"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Don't stand _________ the television. I can't see!",
        "options": [
            "next to",
            "in front of",
            "above",
            "under"
        ],
        "answer": "in front of"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "The police escort came first. The president was in the car _________ it.",
        "options": [
            "on",
            "under",
            "behind",
            "next to"
        ],
        "answer": "behind"
    }
]